我们 是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
噢 我的天哪!
Oh, my goodness!
加油 steven!
Go for it, bro!
这是你的最后一次机会
This is your last chance.
不 不
No, no.
跳 足...兆!
Jump, ju...mp!
-噢!-哎!
-Oh!-Blehh!
在游戏里死好几次也是个体力活
Dying a bunch in a video games is emotionally exhausting.
啥?
Huh?
狮子!
Lion!
把它放下!
Drop it!
狮子 你不能啃它
Lion, you can't chew this up.
我还怎么记住我在
How else am I going to remember the time
乐园骑雷鸟的那段时光啊?
I rode the Thunder Bird at Funland?
好啦 这次不会...
Okay, I'm sure this time--
狮子!
Lion!
休想
Don't even think about it.
既然你不乖 我就把它放到
Since you can't play nice, I'm gonna have to put this
你拿不到的地方:
where you can't get it:
在你的鬃毛里
in your mane.
谢了 伙计
Thank you, boo.
( 好了)
( There we go.)
( 现在它安全了)
( Now, it'll be safe forever)
( 挂在这棵结实的魔法树上)
( hanging in this perfectly stable, magic tree.)
口阿阿阿阿阿!
Ohhhhh!
唔?
Hmm?
口阿阿阿阿阿!
Ahhhhh!
跳 跳
Jump, jump.
我在跳
I am jumping.
我犯了一个严重的的错误!
I made a horrible mistake!
啥?!
What?!
噢 老兄
Aw, man.
等一下 我能补救
Hold on. I can fix it.
啊!
Agh!
铋斯姆
在狮子的鬃毛里有一个宝石人!
There's a Gem inside of Lion's mane!
欢迎关注微博@ UUU字幕组 获取最新熟肉信息!
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
全体
校对
特效
presisco
压制
presisco/ 依依
一个宝石人?
A Gem?
描述一下她
Describe her.
额 等一下
Uh, hang on a sec.
嘿 等等!
Hey, wait!
她很高
She's big.
哈? 嘿 不要走!
Huh? Hey, don't go!
她有彩虹色的头发和纹身
With rainbow hair and tattoos.
彩虹色的头发?
Rainbow hair?
她的宝石是什么样的?
What does her gem look like?
是个内陷的形状?
It's...an innie?
不可能
It can't be.
什么不可能?
Can't be what?
史蒂文 带她出来
Steven, bring her out.
好哒
Okay.
嘿! 朋友
Hey! Little friend.
噢!
Ah!
不要走!
No, don't go!
我好像迷路了 这里只有我们两个
I believe I'm lost and there's no one here but us,
所以帮我一下怎么样?
so how about a little help?
哇! 一个陌生人
Wow! A total stranger.
珍珠...石榴
Pearl...Garnet.
铋-必-斯...女母-姆!
Bi-i-s...mu-u-th!
啊哈哈哈! 你回来了!
Ah ha ha ha! You're back!
哇哦! 嘿!
Whoa! Hey!
我认识的那个珍珠才不会跳进我的怀里
The Pearl I know never jumps into my arms.
嘿 谁家珍珠丢了?
Hey, did somebody lose a pearl?
你属于谁?
Who do you belong to?
谁也不属于
Nobody.
哈哈
Ha ha!
好了 好了 冷静下来
All right, all right. Settle down.
看看是谁在说话
Oh, you're one to talk.
噢 噢 抱歉
Oh, oh, excuse me.
是谁"们"在说话
You're two to talk.
嘿 冷静
Hey, cool it.
你的红宝石性格显露出来了哦
Your ruby is showing.
你去哪了?
Where have you been?
我们以为你被捕了
We thought you'd been captured.
或者更糟 被粉碎了
Or, worse, shattered.
粉碎我? 噗!
Shatter me? Pssh!
母星不能在这颗宝石上留下任何划痕
Homeworld couldn't lay a scratch on this Gem.
咳咳!
Ahem!
这是谁?
Who is this?
大家 这是铋斯姆
Guys, this is Bismuth.
她是最早入队的宝石战士之一
She's one of the original Crystal Gems.
噢 嘿 新成员!
Oh, hey, new recruits!
欢迎加入
Welcome aboard.
我们永远不嫌紫晶太多
We can always use more amethysts.
这个肉丸子是谁?
And who's this meatball?
嗨! 我是史蒂文
Hi. I'm Steven.
你刚才在我的狮子里 现在你在我的房子里
You were in my lion and, now, you're in my house.
好吧 谢谢你收留我
Well, thanks for having me.
我不敢相信!
I can't believe it!
玫瑰说她在金字塔那一战中
Rose said she lost track of you
丢失了你的踪迹
at the battle for the Ziggaurat.
她担心极了!
She was worried sick!
等一下
Wait.
玫瑰呢?
Where is Rose?
嗨 额 实际上 我是玫瑰的儿子
Hi, um. Actually, I'm Rose's son.
她某种意义上变成了我
She kind of turned into me.
我有她的宝石 其他部分来自我爸爸
Well, I have her gem. The rest is from my dad.
哦
Oh.
她在这
There she is.
你...
You...
你认识我吗?
Do you know me?
并不
No.
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
玫瑰的选择不总是很容易理解
It's not always easy understand Rose's choices,
但是我们必须支持她
but we have to stand behind them.
玫瑰真的变成了别人
Rose really is somethin'else.
我是说看看这!
I mean, look at this!
玫瑰真的变成了别人
She really is somethin'else.
哇! 所有的事物都变了!
Wow! Everything's changing!
我们的基地现在是木制的了?
And we're buildin'bases out of wood now?!
这是谁的坏点子?
Whose terrible idea was this?
其他人呢?
And where is everybody else?
其他人?
Everybody else?
是啊 剩余的宝石战士!
Yeah, the rest of the Crystal Gems!
疯狂的老花边 比格斯 雪花
Old Crazy Lace, Biggs, Snowflake.
不
No.
不可能!
No way!
我们刚刚...还在这
We were...just here.
我失踪了多久?
How long was I out?
大约有5300年了
It's been about 5, 300 years.
我们 宝石战士们
We, the Crystal Gems,
成功拯救了地球
were able to save the Earth.
但是我们是仅存的反叛军了不是吗?
But we're all that's left of the Rebellion, huh?
哦 别呀珍珠
Aw, come on, Pearl.
你知道我看不得你哭
You know I can't take it when you cry like that.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不 不需要道歉
No. No need to apologize.
母星对地球最后的攻击
Homeworld's final attack on Earth
毁了所有的宝石战士
wiped out all of the Crystal Gems.
玫瑰设法保护了石榴和我
Rose was able to protect Garnet and myself
看起来
and, by the looks of it,
她也保护了你
she was able to protect you as well.
啊!
Ah!
我就知道那些母星的精英心理扭曲
I knew those Homeworld elites were twisted.
她们粉碎了我们多少人?!
How many of us did they shatter?!
老花边? 比格斯!
Crazy Lace? Biggs!
雪花?!
Snowflake?!
如果我当时在这 我--能阻止他们!
If I was there, I--I could've stopped it!
他们从没停止过尝试
It's not like they've stopped trying.
你说啥?
What's that?
母星从未停止对地球的监视
Homeworld still hasits eyes on this planet.
我们不断粉碎他们的阴谋
We continue to thwarttheir plans,
一遍又一遍
over and over.
但是他们还是不断卷土重来!
But they just keep
coming back!
对 他们超想我们挂掉
Yep, they want us, bad.
不错
Good.
我还以为没有第二次机会
I thought I wouldn't get another chance
来让那些高层昏庸们见识下谁是老大!
to show those upper crusts who's boss!
我们来让他们看看惹恼水晶战士们后会有什么后果!
Let's show 'em what happens when you mess with the Crystal Gems.
棒
Yeah.
铋斯姆 母星的宝石人
Bismuth, the Gems on Homeworld
数量比我们多到不知道哪里去了
outnumber us by a huge amount.
还有他们的科技水平
And their technology far surpasses
也远超地球上的所有
anything we have available on Earth.
这也能算新闻?
What else is new?
石榴 记不记得那次你和我
Garnet, remember when you and I
打掉了一个营的石英战士?
took on a battalion of Quartz soldiers?
走出战场那时候 咱们身上的宝石
We walked out with our stones shining brighter
比战斗前还要闪亮
than when we walked in.
我可是记得咱们打掉了三个营
As I recall, it was three battalions.
还有珍珠 记得那次咱俩停住了那艘登陆舰?
And, Pearl, remember when we stopped that drop ship?
瞧瞧当时那只闪玉脸上的表情!
I'll never forget the look on that Nephrite's face
你直接就把她从那鸡窝里拽出来了!
when you pulled her out of the cockpit!
我记得
I know.
当时她超尴尬的
How embarrassing for her.
哈--哈!
Ha-ha!
现在咱们从落下的地方重新开始吧!
So let's pick up where we left off!
锻造车间 出发!
To the forge!
耶!
Yay!
锻造车间 出发!
To the forge!
喂 啥是锻造车间啊
Yo, what's a forge?
多么令人怀念啊!
That brings back memories, huh?
这就是锻造车间?
Is this the forge?
还没到呢
Not yet.
跟我来
Follow me.
到锻造车间了吗
Is this the forge?
呃 别问我啊 我又没来过
Ugh. Don't ask me. I've never been here before.
嗯 自打铋斯姆失踪之后
Well, since Bismuth was gone,
我们也没来这里的理由了
we've had no reasn to come back here.
可不是吗 这个地方离了我什么都不是
Let's just say this place ain't the same without me.
什么意思
What does that mean?
紫晶! 你觉得那是什么意思?
Amethyst! What do think you that means?
我也不造啊 宝
I don't know, dude.
今天是我第一次见这只宝石人
I've never even seen this Gem before today.
母星把我们打得稀里哗啦
We took a huge blow from Homeworld.
但是今天我们又重新"铋"入正轨了!
But, now, we're back in Bismuth ( business).
她真会讲笑话
She's got jokes!
这就是锻造车间了?
Is this the forge?
差一点
Not quite.
嗒—哒!
Ta-da!
哇哦 瞧瞧这绝赞的大门!
Wow. Now, that's an entrance.
超棒! 铋斯姆!
Bravo, Bismuth!
啊! 铋斯姆!
Aaaah! Bismuth.
哇!
Whoa!
从尺寸看这把剑应该源自"数码宝贝"的奥米加兽
和之前一点没变啊
It's just like I remember it.
这里热得和烤炉一样
It feels like an oven in here.
你以为这就算热了?
You think it's hot now?
对啊 烤炉一样热
Yeah, like an oven.
等下还会更---热呢!
Well, it's about to get way hotter!
赞!
Ah, cool!
哈!
Ooh. Hah!
没什么比淋个岩浆浴更能焕发精神的了
Nothing like a hot lava bath to get into a working mood.
呃 你在这里都做些什么?
Uh, what, exactly, do you do here?
母星使唤我们这些铋斯姆来建造尖塔和庙宇
Homeworld used us Bismuths to erect spires and temples
供那些宝石精英们享受
for the Gem elites to enjoy.
但是玫瑰告诉我们可以主宰自己的命运
But Rose taught me that my life was my own,
可以自己选择
that I could choose
去做
to do
自己想做的所有事
whatever I wanted.
所以我选择做这个
So I chose this.
铋斯姆 你是做...武器的?
Bismuth, you make...weapons?!
不错!
That's right!
我打造了叛军的所有武器
I outfitted the entire Rebellion.
每一件水晶战士们用的武器
Every material weapon used by the Crystal Gems
都是在这里制作的
was made right here in this forge.
等下 那个东西还在吗
Wait. Is it still here?
啊哈! 还在!
Aha! Yes!
给
Here.
这个东西能辅助你出拳
Something to pack a little extra punch.
你为什么不试试三叉戟呢
And why don't you try a trident.
哦 铋斯姆 没必要这么客气
Oh, Bismuth, you shouldn't have.
没啥大不了的
It's no big deal.
我做这些东西好长时间了 自打...
I was working on them since before...
呃 现在给你们也无妨
Well, may as well give them to you now.
等多久都值得
It was worth the wait.
嘿 和你们打交道"铋"然开心啊
Hey, it's a pleasure doing Bismuth with you.
铋斯姆超搞笑的
Bismuth is so funny.
不好说
I don't know.
她一个梗用了两次了
Same joke twice?
嗯 她如果用这个梗三次
Well, it'll be really funny
那才叫搞笑
if she does it a third time.
好吧
Right.
对不起 这个很不好说
Sorry, I--I don't know.
我意思是 她是最初的水晶战士之一
I mean, she's one of the original Crystal Gems
但是却没人提到过她?
and no one ever mentioned her to me,
甚至玫瑰都没说过?
not even Rose?
你不觉得有点 呃
Don't you think that's a little bit, uh..
可疑吗?
suspicious?
是有点奇怪了
I guess that is a little strange.
嘿 小家伙 别以为我把你忘了
Hey, deep cut, don't think I forgot about yo.
你的武器是啥
What you packin'?
哦 这个老物件而已
Oh, this old thing?
哦 哇
Oh, wow.
-怎么了?-额
-What is it?-Well...
没见过别的石英用这种鞭子的
Not every Quartz can make a whip like this.
介意我拿来看下吗?
You mind if I take a look?
随便观赏咯
Knock yourself out.
等下! 我有个主意
Hold on! I've got an idea.
给 有了这个 你破坏力能提升不少
Here. With this, you can really do some damage.
哦液 宝贝儿!
Aw, yeah, baby.
铋斯姆坠棒!
Bismuth's the best!
母星把我们当作泥土看待
Homeworld treats us like dirt
因为我们不像那些精英一般闪耀
because we don't shine like the elites.
但现在水晶战士们卷土重来了
But the Crystal Gems are back
我们会给那些钻石们
and we'll give those Diamonds
一些颜色看看!
another taste of what's coming!
好 现在给我瞧瞧你们有什么能耐 战士们!
Now, show me what you got, soldiers.
噢 我认为这红蓝宝石
Unh! I think the power couple's
失去了她们的力量!
losin'their spark.
谁是下一个?
Who's next?
哈啊—啊—啊!
Ha ha-a-a!
珍珠 我可没让你
Pearl, I don't recall
带给我一支矛
asking you to bring me a spear.
你可不会喜欢我如何把它带给你
You won't like how I give it to you.
哇哦 激光?
Ah! Lasers?
什么时候变成这样的?
When did that happen?
什....
Wha...?!
我要破坏你的"铋"需品!
I'm gonna wreck your Bismuth.
你很有创意
Very creative.
哦耶 我想我还是挺不错的
Yeah, I guess I am pretty great.
这就对了!
That's right!
我们是力量的象征!
We are powerful.
我们是重要的代表!
We are important.
我们是!
We! are!
水晶!
the Crystal
--战士!
Ge-e-e-e-e-ms!
史蒂文 快来让我看看你有什么能耐
Steven, come down and show me what you're made of!
噢 我会的 但这对我来说太激烈了
Uh, I would, but this is a little intense for me.
这可是我们在战斗之前
But it's a ritual for us Crystal Gems
所需的试炼
to spar before battle.
事实上 我有一些更好的
Well, actually, I have some rituals
训练方法
I like a little better.
噢是吗?
Oh, yeah?
让我瞧瞧
Let me see 'em.
什么...
Wha...?
传说中的充满力量的恶魔之刃
The powerful, legendary demon blade,
被村正附体...
possessed by Muramasa.
一旦我拥有了这把恶魔之刃 我就能成为
With this demon blade, I will be
世界上最强大的战士!
the most powerful fighter in all the world!
不! 孤刃 不要使用它!
No, Lonely Blade! Don't use it!
什么?
What?
如果那把刀真有无穷的力量
If that thing's got infinite power,
孤刃肯定使用它啊
then, of courseLonely Blade should use it.
这肯定说得通
It just makes sense.
不需要说通
It doesn't have to make sense.
这只是演戏而已
It's entertainment.
无穷的...
Infinite...
力量!!!
powe-e-e-e-r!
铋斯姆今晚你可以在这里休息
Bismuth, you can chill out here tonight
如果你想的话你还能睡一觉
and...sleep, if you want to.
你知道吗
You know what?
我决定试一试
I think I'll give it a try.
我喜欢水晶战士的这些新惯例
I like these new Crystal Gem rituals.
你知道的 通常我遇上一个新的宝石
You know, usually, when I meet a new Gem,
她们通常都试图干掉我 跟她们混熟
they try and kill me and it takes me forever
简直要用一辈子时间
to become friends with them.
我的意思是 我很高兴你能加入我们
I guess I mean I'm really glad you're here.
我也是
Me, too.
我很高兴能再有一次机会重来
Glad to have another chance.
那明天
So, tomorrow, you gonna show me
你要向我展示你在战场上有什么本事吗?
what you goton the battlefield?
哦 我是可以
Oh, I mean, I-I would,
不过我的武器大多都是防御用的
but, most of my weapons are for defense.
噢! 除了那一个
Oh, except for one.
玫瑰的剑
Rose's sword.
我最好的作品
My finest piece of work.
你制造了它?
You made this?
你真的不记得了 对吧
You really don't remember, huh?
玫瑰石英改变了我的一生
Rose Quartz changed my life.
我刚来到地球时认为这里不过是另一个殖民地
I came to Earth thinking this was just another colony.
建造竞技场训练那些精英的战士
Build another arena for important fighters to fight in,
建造尖塔给重要的冥想者去思考
build another spire for important thinkers to think in,
然后 我遇见了她
and then, I met her.
她只是一名石英战士 诞生于这片土地
Just another Quartz soldier, made right here in the dirt,
但她却与众不同
but she was different.
因为她选择了一条不同的道路
And she was different because she decided to be.
她问我 什么是我想去创造的
And she asked me what I wanted to build,
而我以前从未听过这样的话
and I'd never heard that before.
宝石们从来没听过她们可以选择自己的命运
And Gems never hear they can be anything
但是玫瑰为我们打开了新的大门
other than what they are, but Rose opened our eyes.
大家总是告诉我我的母亲有多么优秀
Everybody always tells mehow great Mom was.
我感觉自己永远比不上她
I just don't feel like Ican ever measure up to her.
我真是不敢相信
I can't believe this,
我会在这里鼓励玫瑰的...
that I'm the one givingthe pep talk to Rose's...
玫瑰的?
Rose's...?
儿子
Son.
对
Right.
你是与众不同的
You are different.
这就是重点
That's what's so exciting.
你不需要像玫瑰石英一样
You don't have to be like Rose Quartz.
你能够成为比她更优秀的人
You can be someoneeven better.
你能够做你自己
You can be you.
还有你知道吗
And you know what?
你理应得到更好的武器
You deserve an even better weapon.
我设计这把剑为的是一场公平的较量
I designed this swordfor a fair fight.
它可以瞬间穿透宝石人的身体
It can cut through a Gem's physical form in an instant!
但不能破坏宝石本体
Destroying the body, but never the Gem.
好厉害
Cool.
然而
But...
母星从不公平对待战争
Homeworld doesn't fight fair.
这就是我们需要不同战略的原因
That's why we need a different strategy.
喔 哇
Ohh. Whoa.
我之前在做一个能够改变战争局势的武器
I was working on a weapon thatwould've been a gamechanger.
母星知道怎么一击必杀
Homeworld knows how to hit us where it counts,
但我们可以做到她们能做到的一切 甚至更好
but we can do everythingthey can do, and better.
就是这个 这件可以给我们带来胜利的武器
Here it is: the weapon that would've won the war.
"断裂极限"的造型与功能类似"The Big O"( 魅影巨神) 中Big O的针筒拳
哇噢噢噢!
Whoa!
这是什么?
What is it?
我叫它"断裂极限"
I call it a Breaking Point.
赞! 它能做什么?
Cool! What does it do?
好好瞧着吧
Just watch.
哈!
Hah!
听好了 你们这些母星的昏君
Listen up, you Homeworld upper crusts!
我们! 可是!
We! are!
宝石!
the Crystal
战士!
Gems!
啊!
Unh!
所以 你怎么看?
So, what do you think?
你......你粉碎了它
Y-You shattered it.
没错!
That's right!
这个神器可以一眨眼的瞬间
One shot from this baby will shatter any Gem
粉碎星系中任何一个宝石
in the galaxy, in the blink of an eye.
粉碎本体意味着永远消灭宝石人
Shattering a Gem would destroy them forever.
当然!
Exactly!
母星的家伙们
The Homeworld Gems won't be able
被打成碎片后就不能占领地球了
to retake this planet when they're reduced to shards.
这儿
There.
* 此处为双关语 bismuth为business 你现在已经准备充分了
现在 * 你可真像个真正意义上的铋斯姆
Now, you look like you really mean Bismuth.
瞧瞧 这才叫真正的武器
Now, that's a real weapon.
为何你不给它一次测试射?
Why don't you give it a test run?
这玩意儿就是你的专属测试目标啦
This one's got your name on it.
等下 让我靠边站站
Wait, let me get out of your way.
呼呜!
Hooh!
唉 铋斯姆 我不能用这个
Ah. Bismuth, I can't use this.
你说什么?
What?
为什么不行?
Why not?
粉碎宝石
Shattering Gems,
做了这个我们和母星的人不是没有区别了吗?
wouldn't that make us the same as Homeworld?
当然有!
Of course not!
我们粉碎他们是因为我们拥有正义的理由与目的!
We'd be shattering them for the sake of our cause,
为了守护我们的盟军! 我们的朋友!
to protect our allies, our friends,
为了让所有的宝石从母星的暴政中获得自由!
to free all Gems from Homeworld's tyranny!
可它...
It's just, it--
这不是一个宝石战士会去做的
it's not what a Crystal Gem would do.
不用告诉我一个宝石战士会去做些什么
Don't tell me what a Crystal Gem would do.
我这个宝石战士名副其实
Nobody's more Crystal Gem than I am.
如果你不用它 那么就我用
If you won't take it, I'll just use it myself.
不行! 没有人能用它!
No! No one is using it!
对不起 铋斯姆 但这不对
I'm sorry, Bismuth, but it's not right.
她也曾如此说过
That's exactly what she said.
哈?
Huh?
就如同你这般说的
That's exactly what you said.
呃 呃嗯...
Uh, uh...
是你对吧 玫瑰?
It is you, isn't it, Rose?
你-你到底在说什么?
Wha-What are you talking about?
别骗我
Don't lie to me.
你在隐瞒了一切后
You can't expect me to believe you now,
就不要指望我再相信你了
after you lied about everything?
你隐藏了你的新形态
You're lying about this new form,
就像你向她们隐瞒着我的事!
just like you lied to the others about me!
但我还没消失 对不对?
But I didn't just disappear, did I?
你明明知道在我身上发生过什么!
You know what happened to me!
-嗯!-哈啊!
-Mnh!-Unh!
啊!
Uh!
等等! 铋斯姆!
Wait! Bismuth!
这是个天大的误会!
This is just a big misunderstanding!
骗子! 不要和我玩游戏 玫瑰
Liar! Don't play games with me, Rose.
当时我们就在这个地方
We were right. here.
我曾经在这儿告诉你成功的秘诀 但你拒绝了
I offered you the secret to victory, and you refused.
断裂极限将会改变所有
The Breaking Point would've changed everything.
我不想与你战斗
I didn't want to fight you,
可你让我无路! 可走!
but you left me no! choice!
什么样的领袖
What type of leader
会不给她的军队可以获胜的机会?!
doesn't give her army the best chance to win?!
哈! 哈!
Ah! Ah!
你怎么可以珍视敌人
How could you value the gems of our enemies
多过我们?
more than our own?
看看没有我你都做成了点什么
And look what you've done without me,
没有断裂极限!
without the Breaking Point!
哈! 哈!
Ah! Ah!
你......输了!
You...lost!
啊!
Ah!
啊嗯嗯嗯嗯!
Annnnh!
呜哇!
Unh.
等-等等 我不是我妈妈!
W-Wait. I'm not my mom!
我-我不知道她到底做了些什么
I-I don't know what she did,
但是 我确信她不是想要伤害你
but, I'm sure she didn't want to hurt you.
太迟了
It's too late.
我再也不会相信你了!
I don't believe you anymore!
呵 哈!
Huh! Huh!
你说的那些话 那些关于宝石们可以
All that talk about how Gems could take control
掌控自己身份的话
of their own identities,
那些宝石们不该忽视自身潜力的话
how we'd been convinced to ignore our own potential.
啊! 好烫!
Ah! Hot!
仅此而已 不是吗?
That's all it was, wasn't it?
说说而已! 啊!
Just! talk! Unh!
呃啊!
Uh!
你应该听从于我 玫瑰
You should've listened to me, Rose.
我早就会向母星发起战争
I would've taken the war to Homeworld
并摧毁那些钻石!
and shattered the Diamonds.
我早就能解放--
I would've liberated--
呵! 每个人!
unh!--everyone.
啊!
Ah!
呃!
Unh!
呃啊!
Ah!
呃啊啊! 铋斯姆 看! 招!
Annh! Bismuth, watch! out!
呃呃!
Uh!
哦!
Oh.
啊--!
Aggh!
铋斯姆 别这样
Bismuth, this has to stop.
所以呢? 你要怎样? 粉碎我?
So, what are you gonna do, shatter me?
上啊!
Go ahead!
粉碎我!
Just do it!
不!
No!
即使我们不能达成共识 也没有人应当被粉碎
Even if we don't agree, nobody deserves this.
哼!
Uhh.
哈!
Uh!
你当初就应该粉碎了我
You should've shattered me back then.
至少 如果我成为了碎片 便不知道
At least, if I were in pieces, I wouldn't have to know
我在你的心中是多么的无足轻重
how little I mattered to you.
你甚至没有告诉她们
You didn't even tell them.
你把我泡泡收容后甚至没有告诉你的伙伴们--
You bubbled me away and didn't ever tell your friends--
我的伙伴
my friends.
我会告诉她们的
I'm going to tell them.
我会告诉她们所有事情
I'm gonna tell them everything.
你真的比她好太多
Then you really are better than her.
这里的镜头与"终结者2"中约翰·康纳将终结者的机械臂扔到钢水中类似
史蒂文!
Steven!
哦 嘿 伙计
Oh, hey, dude.
-哦!-昂?
-Oh!-What?
这有一些事情我需要告诉你们
There's something I need to tell you.